online-toolz.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy - Online Toolz

Last updated: 01 Feb, 2011 

### What types of information do we collect?

All information collected by OnlineToolz is Anonymous information, meaning that it does not lead to your personal information ( ex: your name or your address ) it is just enough information to differentiate between different users accessing the website 

### What information do we collect specifically ?

Whenever you visit OnlineToolz, we collect the following: 

**Visitor Information**   
1- IP (Internet Protocol) address   
2- The address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through OnlineToolz   
3- Your browser information (ex: Firefox, Chrome ..etc)   
4- Your OS (Operating System) name/version 

### Do we use Cookies ?

No, but Third Party Services may do 

### Third Party Services

This website uses analytics and advertising services (and/or other services) provided by third parties, in general they collect the same amount of visitor information (Not search information) as we collect, but please note that they may collect other information – that we are not aware of - as well   
Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of cookie data that such third parties may collect from you. These third parties will treat your cookie data in accordance with their own policies as to data collection, retention and usage, and we have no control over such policies. 

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to be sure you are familiar with the most current version. The Privacy Policy will state the date it was last amended at the top of the page. 

Should You have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, You may contact OnlineToolz using the Contacts link
